http://buffalosoldier.nu/index.php?main_page=privacy

T-Shirts
All Products ...
Sponsors
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Welcome to Buffalo SoldierWe are a one-stop source for books, clothing, hats and caps, prints, sculptures, unit patches, weapons and equipment. We are committed to protecting your privacy in all aspects of our business and hope you will take the time to read this privacy policy. It explains what information we collect from you and how we use that information. By using our Web site or purchasing products or services from us, you agree to be bound by this policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. You are invited to check back periodically!Information we collect and how we use itWhen you order from us, we ask for your name, shipping address, email address, telephone number, and your credit card number, billing address, and expiration date (your "Order Information"). This information is necessary for us to process your order and to notify you of your order status. We may use your Account Information and Order Information to occasionally notify you about important changes to the Web site, new Buffalo Soldier features, or special Buffalo Soldier offers you may find useful.How we protect your informationThis Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. When you place orders or access your account information, we use a secure server.
Buffalo Soldier will not share your personal information with third parties unless the disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process, (2) protect and defend our rights and property, (3) protect our customers or users from misuse or unauthorized use of the Buffalo Soldier Web site, or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our customers or the public.Links to other Web sitesThe Buffalo Soldier Web site may contain links to other sites, operated by third parties, that we think may be of interest to you. Buffalo Soldier encourages third parties to follow appropriate privacy standards and policies, but is not responsible for the actions of those parties, the content of their Web sites, or any products or services they may offer.How to contact usBuffalo Soldier welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send email to uscav@maxxconnecton.net
Home
Copyright © 2020 Buffalo Soldier. Powered by Zen Cart
